Guide to the David J. Skorton Presidential Liaison records, 2006-2014.
Skorton, David J. papers
- Series I. Meetings and Briefings
  - Meeting with Greg Galvin and Phil Proujansky (FUCHS), February 5, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Alison Yu, Hearst Fnd., February 9, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Yossie Hollander, February 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Alan and Betsey Harris, February 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Dinner hosted by Alan and Elizabeth Harris, February 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Lunch meeting with Howard Milstein, February 12, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Reception hosted by Ken and Barbara Horowitz, February 12, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Investment Committee Meeting, February 13, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Larry Salameno, February 17, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Lunch dedication for George Gellert, February 18, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Parents Fund Committee Winter Meeting (FUCHS), February 19, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Microsoft/Video Conference with Frank Holland, February 24, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Barbara Novick, March 1, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Weill/Veterinary College Reception, March 2, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Howard Milstein, March 4, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Lunch meeting with Hank Greenberg, March 5, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Video Message – Asia Leadership Conference, March 9, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with David Croll, March 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Bob Abrams (FUCHS), March 16, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Dinner and Overnight with Irwin and Joan Jacobs, March 17, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to George Gellert (FUCHS), March 17, 2010 (Box 5)
  - San Francisco Kick-off Event, March 18, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Cornell Silicon Valley Advisory Board Meeting, March 18, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with John Dyson, March 25, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Susan Hakkarainen (FUCHS), April 1, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with David Croll (FUCHS), April 8, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Event honoring Linda Macaulay, April 8, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Breakfast meeting with Harris Rosen, April 10, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Hank Greenberg, April 14, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Lubna Olayan, April 15, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Tisch Power Breakfast (FUCHS), April 15, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Foremost Benefactor Ceremony for David and Betty Ann Solinger (FUCHS), April 19, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to Rich Booth, April 22, 2010 (Box 5)
  - CALS Advisory Council Dinner (FUCHS), April 22, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Moujan Vahdat (FUCHS), April 23, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Parents Campus Visit Reception (FUCHS), April 23, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Parents Campus Visit Welcome, April 23, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Martin Tang (FUCHS), April 23, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Lunch with Roy Park, April 29, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Phone call with Howard Milstein, April 29, 2010 (Box 5)
  - President’s Council on Cornell Women (PCCW) 20th Anniversary Dinner, April 30, 2010 (Box 5)
  - PCCW Welcome (FUCHS), April 30, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Cathy Merrill Williams (FUCHS), April 30, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Adam Levinson, April 30, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Cornell University Religious Works, May 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with David Kennedy, May 14, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to Irwin Jacobs, May 15, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with David and Pat Atkinson (FUCHS), May 17, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Student Phoning Program Lunch (DAVISSON), May 17, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Breakfast with David and Pat Atkinson, May 18, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Phone call to Allan Tessler, May 24, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Dinner with Phil Young (FUCHS), May 27, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Eileen Walker, May 27, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Lunch meeting with Ratan Tata, May 28, 2010 (Box 5)
  - 2010 Senior Class Campaign Final Reception, May 28, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Ratan Tata (FUCHS), May 28, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Board of Trustees Friday Dinner, May 28, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Board of Trustees Faculty Dinner, May 29, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with George Gellert, June 2, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Tanner Prize Luncheon, June 4, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Irene Rosenfeld and Richard Illgen, June 4, 2010 (Box 5)
  - ICON of the Industry Awards, June 8, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Dick Loynd, June 10, 2010 (Box 5)
  - College of Vet Med Reception, June 10, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Martin Tang Classroom Dedication, June 10, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1935, 1940, and 1945 Reception, June 10, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1950 Dinner, June 10, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Olin Luncheon, June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Engineering Dean’s Breakfast (FUCHS), June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Andrew Kessler (FUCHS), June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Cornell Wall Street Reunion, June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Olin Giving Reception (FUCHS), June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with John Mellowes (FUCHS), June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1950 Carnauba Film Intro, June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Olin Lecture, June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1975 Reception, June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1970 Dinner, June 11, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1955 Lunch, June 12, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1985 Reception, June 12, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Cornell Asian Alumni Association (CAAA) Reception, June 12, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1950 Dinner, June 12, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Cornelliana Night, June 12, 2010 (Box 5)
  - State of the University Address, June 12, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Chuck Feeney, June 17, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Jan Rock Zubrow, June 18, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Meeting with Ira Drukier, June 18, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Lunch with Hank Greenberg, July 14, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Andrew Boas, July 14, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Linda Macaulay, July 14, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast with John Dyson (FUCHS), July 15, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Ken Goldman (FUCHS), July 16, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Narayana Murthy, July 17, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Yossie Hollander, July 19, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Irene Rosenfeld/Richard Illgen, July 22, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Mitch Gitin (FUCHS), July 26, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ned Morgens, July 28, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Rob Dyson, July 29, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Gara LaMarche, July 30, 2010 (Box 6)
  - The Hartwell Foundation (FUCHS), August 12, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Dinner hosted by Don and Judy Opatrny, August 16, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Seth Klarman, August 17, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast meeting with Jeff Parker, August 17, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Peter Robbins, August 18, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with John Foote (FUCHS), August 19, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Alumni Parent Legacy Reception, August 21, 2010 (Box 6)
  - PCAM: Dinner with President Emeriti, September 12, 2010 (Box 6)
  - PCAM: Welcome, September 13, 2010 (Box 6)
  - PCAM: Sesquicentennial Talk (FUCHS), September 13, 2010 (Box 6)
  - PCAM: Group Photo and Private Mtg, September 13, 2010 (Box 6)
  - PCAM: Dinner hosted by DJS/RLD, September 13, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with David Litman, September 13, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Jack Clarke, September 14, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Chairman’s Circle Dinner, September 15, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with David Fischell, September 17, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Carolyn Landis, September 20, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Drukier Celebration, September 20, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Peter Sacerdote, September 22, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Andy Paul, September 22, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ratan Tata, September 23, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Solomon Kerzner, September 24, 2010 (Box 6)
  - FHTREASA Reception and Dinner, September 24, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Lynch/Weiss Welcome, September 25, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Lynch/Weiss Luncheon (FUCHS), September 25, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Jacqueline Novogratz, September 27, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Jim McCormick (FUCHS), September 28, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Hartwell Foundation Event, September 29, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Visit with Keith Sinclair Scholars, September 29, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Dinner with Bob and Helen Appel, September 30, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bob and Helen Appel (FUCHS), September 30, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Robert A. Paul, September 30, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with George and Barbara Gellert, October 1, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bob and Helen Appel, October 1, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Dyson School Celebration, October 1, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Reception and Dinner hosted by Donald Miller, October 5, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Phone call with Leonard Litwin, October 2010 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast with Karen Burke, October 8, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Knight Scholars Luncheon, October 19, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Strategic Planning Dinner – Patti Harris, October 20, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Susan Patricoff, October 22, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast mtg w/Fred Elghanayan, October 22, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with David and Cheryl Einhorn, October 22, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Don Opatrny (FUCHS), October 28, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Campaign Cabinet Meeting and Committee on Development Meeting (FUCHS), October 28, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Atkinson Panel, October 28, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Martin Tang, October 28, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Reception and Dinner honoring David Atkinson, October 28, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with the Atkinson Family, October 28, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Joint Annual Meeting, October 29, 2010 (Box 6)
  - TCAM: Friday Dinner, October 29, 2010 (Box 6)
  - A Salute to the Best and the Brightest, October 29, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Cornell Annual Fund Breakfast, October 30, 2010 (Box 6)
  - San and Jo Reis Memorial Reception, October 30, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Hank Greenberg, November 4, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Lubna Olayan, November 4, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast meeting with Bobby Abrams (FUCHS), November 4, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Lewis Wirshba, November 5, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Credit Suisse Luncheon, November 5, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Tom Groos, November 2010 (Box 6)
  - Dinner with Jacob Scholars (FUCHS), November 7, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Konvitz Lecuture, November 8, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Irwin and Joan Jacobs, November 8, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Allison Yu, Hearst Fdn., November 9, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Hatfield Lecture, November 11, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Fred Young (FUCHS), November 11, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Harris Rosen, November 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Henry M. Paulson, Jr., November 11, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Swanson Dedication Event, November 11, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Hatfield Lecture, Reception and Dinner, November 11, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Phone call with Gara LaMarche, November 12, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Houston All-Alumni Reception, November 17, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Campaign Celebration Event in Boston, MA, November 18, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Percy Browning (FUCHS), November 18, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast meeting with David Croll, November 19, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Seth Klarman, November 19, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast with Steve and Barbara Friedman, November 30, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Mariet Westermann, Mellon Fdn. (FUCHS), December 2, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with John Neu (FUCHS), December 8, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Don Opatrny (FUCHS), December 8, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Strategic Planning Dinner hosted by Sandy and Joan Weill, December 9, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, December 10, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Chuck Feeney, December 10, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Univ. Wyomings VP’s (FUCHS), January 6, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bob Berry and Tom Buchanan, January 6, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bob Appel, January 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Fisk Johnson, January 18, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Predictions Dinner, January 18, 2011 (Box 6)
  - President’s Circle Dinner, January 19, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bill Marriott, January 24, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Cornell Alumni Leadership Luncheon, January 29, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Howard Milstein, February 4, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Fritz SchwarzMeeting with Fritz Schwarz, February 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Investment Committee Meeting, February 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bob Appel, February 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Judy Biggs, February 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dinner hosted by David Skorton, February 13, 2011 (Box 6)
  - All Alumni Brunch, February 13, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with John and Melissa Ceriale, February 14, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Reception and Dinner hosted by Lee and Mary Pillsbury, February 14, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Tom and Diann Mann, February 14, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Jack Clarke, February 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Al and Betsey Harris, February 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dinner hosted by Alan and Betsey Harris, February 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Curtis and Pamela Reis (FUCHS), February 18, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Tisch Strategic Planning Dinner, March 2, 2011 (Box 6)
  - International Rankings, March 3, 2011 (Box 6)
  - PCCW Friday Dinner, March 4, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Martin Tang, March 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Tata Nano Presentation and Reception), March 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast mtg w/Ratan Tata and Alice Pell (FUCHS), March 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - LA Campaign Kickoff, March 14, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with David Duffield and Amy Zeifang, March 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - CSV11 Event, March 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Andy Verhalen, March 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - CSV Advisors Luncheon, March 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Irwin and Joan Jacobs, March 16, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Becky and Jim Morgan (FUCHS), March 16, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Stephen and Evalyn Milman, March 18, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ira Drukier, March 22, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Sam Fleming (FUCHS), March 31, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Alumni Candidates, April 6, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Sherri Stuewer, April 7, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Stephen and Nancy Einhorn, April 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dinner with David and Pat Atkinson (FUCHS), April 13, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with David and Pat Atkinson (FUCHS), April 14, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ratan Tata, April 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dinner hosted by Ratan Tata, April 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Chuck Feeney, April 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dinner hosted by Dr. Fahad Al-Mubarak, April 18, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Jeff MacCorkle (FUCHS), April 24, 2011 (Box 6)
  - CC of Beijing Reception (FUCHS), April 24, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Semester Prize Lunch, April 26, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Mtg with Larry and Judith Tanenbaum, April 28, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Parents Campus Visit Welcome, April 29, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Visit with Peter Mok, April 29, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bobby Abrams (FUCHS), May 5, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Tower Club Reception, May 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bob Appel, May 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Dick Schwartz, May 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Barbara Novick, May 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dinner with Jim and Meryl Tisch, May 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Jack Clarke, May 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Frank Robinson Retirement Celebration (FUCHS), May 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bobby Abrams, May 13, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with David and Mary Solomon, May 13, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Phone call to Cathy Merrill Williams, May 13, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Merrill Scholars Lunch, May 25, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Doug Merrill, May 25, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Irene Rosenfeld (FUCHS), May 26, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Senior Class Campaign Reception, May 27, 2011 (Box 6)
  - BoT Friday Dinner, May 27, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Larry and Theresa Salameno, June 1, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Jan Rock Zubrow, June 6, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with David and Cheryl Einhorn, June 6, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Tanner Prize 2011, June 6, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with the Hilton Family, June 7, 2011 (Box 6)
  - ICON of the Industry Event, June 7, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Alvin Ailey Event, June 8, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Combined Class Reception, June 9, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Chuck and Helga Feeney, June 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Chuck Feeney, June 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1976 Dinner, June 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1971 40th Reunion, June 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1966 45th Breakfast, June 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Olin Lecture, June 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1951 Reception, June 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1981 Lunch, June 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - State of the University Address, June 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1961 Dinner, June 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Cornelliana Night, June 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Steve Altman ’71 Memorial Bench Dedication, June 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - FB Ceremony for Ken Goldman, June 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1986 Reception, June 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ronni Lacroute (FUCHS), June 13, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Richard Meier and Peter Eisenman, June 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Alumni Reception hosted by Mariani Family, June 19, 2011 (Box 6)
  - IVY Plus Conference, June 21, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Irwin and Joan Jacobs Event (FUCHS), June 21, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Groos FB Ceremony, June 22, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Kwee Family Visit, June 22, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Fritz Schwarz, July 1, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Robert Ziff, July 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Roy Park, July 18, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Phone call with Lubna Olayan, July 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Howard Milstein (FUCHS), July 19, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dinner with John and Janet Swanson (FUCHS), July 21, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Jim McCormick, July 28, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Phone call with Bart Winokur, July 28,2011 (Box 6)
  - Foremost Benefactor Ceremony for Peter Nolan (FUCHS), August 1, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dedication Reception for Peter Nolan (FUCHS), August 1, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Bill Kay, August 19, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Legacy Breakfast, August 20, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast with John and Elaine Alexander, August 26, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Mike Zak, August 26, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Seth Klarman, August 26, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dedication – Bill Nye Solar Noon Clock, August 27, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dinner hosted by Ronay and Richard Menschel, September 1, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Chairman’s Circle Dinner, September 7, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Joint MG Meeting, September 7, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Merryl Tisch, September 8, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast with Najib Canan (FUCHS), September 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - PCAM: DJS welcome to PC’s, September 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Private mtg w/Presidential Councillors, September 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - PCAM: Dinner hosted by DJS, September 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Jack Clarke, September 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Allan Tessler, September 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - FHTR Awards Dinner, September 16, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Big Red Band Tailgate, September 17, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Coin Toss – Homecoming Football Game, September 17, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Desh Deshpande and Raj Melville, September 19, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Desh and Jaishree Deshpande (FUCHS), September 19, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with David Atkinson, September 19, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Phone call with Don Randel, September 23, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lynch Weiss Welcome Videotaping, September 23, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Bill Marriott, September 23, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Prof. Harold Scheraga Ceremony, September 23, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Mullestein Award Rec honoring Bob Staley, September 24, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Susan Bell (HP), October 7, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Hank Greenberg, October 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ira Drukier, October 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - FB Ceremony for Don and Muffy Miller, October 11, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Johnson Museum Grand Opening, October 14, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ivan Lustig (FUCHS), October 19, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Richard and Lisa Baker, October 20, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Wine and Dine Event, October 20, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Atkinson Ctr Ext. Adv. Board Meeting, October 20, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Introduce Rem Koolhaas, October 20, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Humanities Presentation, October 21, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Joint Annual Meeting, October 21, 2011 (Box 6)
  - TCAM: Friday Night Dinner, October 21, 2011 (Box 6)
  - RLD Panel Moderator – TCAM, October 21, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Cornell Annual Fund Breakfast, October 22, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Fritz Schwartz, November 3, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Ed Meyer, November 10, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Dinner hosted by Bob and Laura Langer, November16, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Boston Alumni Breakfast, November 17, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with David Croll, November 17, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Sam Fleming, November 17, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Neal, Christine and Michele Douglas (FUCHS), November 21, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ratan Tata, December 1, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Andy Paul, December 12, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ronay and Richard Menschel, December 14, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with George Gellert, December 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Tony Wang, December 15, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Martin Tang, January 4, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Tea with Martin Tang and Guests, January 4, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Dinner hosted by Walter and Wendy Kwok, January 4, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Jia “Jonathan” Zhu and Ruby Ye, January 4, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Morgan Sze, January 5, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast with Warren Allderige, January 5, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Lunch hosted by Fiona Ip and Donald Li, January 5, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Hong Kong All Alumni Reception and Dinner, January 5, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Adam and Brittany Levinson, January 6, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Dinner hosted by Liong Phing and Teck Ai Kwee, January 6, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Lunch hosted by Rohet and Arshna Tolani, January 7, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Singapore All Alumni Dinner, January 7, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Shanghai All Alumni Reception, January 8, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Phil Liao, January 8, 2012 (Box 6)
  - President’s Circle Dinner, January 18, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Major Gifts Committee Lunch, January 18, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ratan Tata, January 21, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Phone call w/Harold and Lynne Handler (FUCHS), January 25, 2012 (Box 6)
  - DC All Alumni Campaign Luncheon, January 25, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Breakfast with Cathy Merrill Williams, January 28, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Phone call with Allan Tessler (FUCHS), February 3, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Lunch meeting with Mike Zak (FUCHS), February 7, 2012 (Box 6)
  - AAD All Staff Reception, February 7, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Senior Class Campaign Kickoff Rec., February 9, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Visit with Curtis and Pamela Reis (FUCHS), February 10, 2012 (Box 6)
  - President’s Circle Conference Call (FUCHS), February 10, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Ken Kahn, February 17, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Meeting with Leonard Harlan, February 17, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Tom and Diann Mann, February 17, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Cocktail Reception hosted by John and Melissa Ceriale, February 17, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Investment Committee Meeting, February 18, 2012 (Box 6)
  - Lunch with Judy Biggs, February 19, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Art Wolcott, February 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Cornell Club of Sarasota Luncheon, February 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Dinner hosted by Al and Betsey Harris, February 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Phone call w/Patrick Gerschel (FUCHS), February 21, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast with Jack Clarke, February 21, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Chris Oeschli, February 22, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Ira Drukier, February 22, 2012 (Box 7)
  - PCCW Friday Dinner, March 2, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Address by Sen. Kirsten Gillibrand, March 2, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Hatfield Reception/Dinner – Irene Rosenfeld, March 7, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Hatfield Lecture – Irene Rosenfeld, March 7, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Irene Rosenfeld, March 7, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Milstein Hall Donor Recognition Dinner, March 9, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast with Irwin and Joan Jacobs, March 13, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Ann Bowers, March 13, 2012 (Box 7)
  - CSV Advisors Lunch, March 13, 2012 (Box 7)
  - CSV12, March 14, 2012 (Box 7)
  - CSV Advisors Dinner, March 14, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Andy Paul, March 19, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with David and Cheryl Einhorn, March 19, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast meeting with Andrew Tisch, March 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Sam Fleming (FUCHS), March 29, 2012 (Box 7)